<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mobin</string>
    <string name="app_title">Mobin Health</string>
    <string name="still">Still</string>
    <string name="walking">Walking</string>
    <string name="running">Running</string>
    <string name="cycling">Cycling</string>
    <string name="vehicle">On Vehicle</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="my_preference_key">preferences_key</string>

    <string name="location_services">Location Services</string>
    <string name="location_services_permission">I understand and agree that GPS data, provided by the location services on the mobile device, will be gathered by the Moving Health App and used to calculate measurements of mobility (average walking speed, distance walked each day, motor vehicle trips each day, time in motor vehicles each day).</string>
    <string name="location_services_title_one">Physical Activity and Location Services</string>
    <string name="location_services_title_two">Physical Activity and Location Services</string>
    <string name="locationservices_dialog_message">The app requires the use of Location Services in order to work properly. Please enable Location Services.</string>
    <string name="only_for">Before continuing, make sure to read and accept the Terms and Conditions.\n\nThen, we\'ll ask you to switch on the phone\'s motion and fitness sensors and the location detection. \n \nIt will take just a few seconds and it will make sure the app provides you with the best possible experience.</string>
    <string name="open_permissions">Open Permissions</string>
    <string name="paragraph_third_about_set_up">Please read and accept our Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">A smartphone study of activity and mobility in people with and without disease</string>

    <string name="heart_minutes">♥ minutes</string>
    <string name="move_minutes">move minutes</string>
    <string name="steps">steps</string>

    <string name="participant_information">Participant Information</string>
    <string name="participant_information_and_policy">Participant Information and Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_1">Please note: this policy applies only to consumers downloading the app from the app stores. If you are using the app in a professional role as part of one of the associated programmes (e.g. Mobilise-D), the policy may be regulated by the specific programme. You are required to refer to the programme documentation.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_10">Your Rights To Delete Your Personal Data</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_11">If at any time you want to leave the programme and your data to be removed, you can do this from within the app, under Menu > Help > Contact Us and filling the  form specifying that you want your data to be removed from our servers. Please note:  we will only be able to delete your data if you contact us from within the app, as this will provide us with your unique id which is necessary to identify your data in our databases. If you do not use the app to contact us or if you uninstall the app, we will NOT be able to identify your data and hence we will be unable to delete it. Note that if you uninstall the app and then reinstall it, the unique user Id will be different, so we will only be able to identify the data the app has collected after the last installation.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_12">Data Security</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_13">We work hard to keep your data safe. We use a combination of technical, administrative, and physical controls to maintain the security of your data. As a reason of security, data is only transmitted from the phone to our servers and never back. Moreover, we use Transport Layer Security (“TLS”) to encrypt the data. No method of transmitting or storing data is completely secure, however. If you have a security-related concern, please contact us via the Help menu. </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_14">Who has ethically reviewed the project?</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_15">This project has been ethically approved via the project coordinators, The University of Sheffield’s Computer Science department’s ethics review procedure. The University’s Research Ethics Committee monitors the application and delivery of the University’s Ethics Review Procedure across the University meeting ethical guidelines for EU research.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_16">European Privacy Disclosure</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_17">If you live in the European Economic Area (EEA), United Kingdom (UK), or Switzerland, please review these additional privacy disclosures under the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).\nData Controller: is The University of Sheffield, Firth Court, Western Bank, S10 2NT Sheffield, United Kingdom.\nHealth data: we do not ask for any health data, unless you participate in a specific programme. In that case, see the disclosure of the specific programme.\nBasis for processing: For personal data subject to the GDPR, our legal basis is consent and public utility.\nHow to exercise your legal rights: Please see our Terms and Conditions and Sections on your rights above. If you want to access or remove your data, please  contact us via the app via Menu > Help > Contact us for any requests. Please note:  as we keep your data in an anonymous format, we will only be able to identify your data if you contact us from within the app, as this will provide us with your unique id which is necessary to identify your data in our databases. If you do not use the app to contact us or if you uninstall the app, we will NOT be able to identify your data and hence we will be unable to access it or delete it. Note that if you uninstall the app and then reinstall it, the unique user Id will be different, so we will only be able to identify the data the app has collected after the last installation.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_18">Contact for further information</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_19">Please use the app feedback tool. Otherwise use the email address listed on the Google Play/Apple iTunes pages.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_2">Information we collect</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_3">Your location data collected in the background 24/7 (e.g. via sensors like the GPS receiver or the network antenna)\nYour activities parameters such as steps, accelerometer data, etc. collected 24/7\nDaily activities, such as walking, running, etc.\nDepending on the programme you subscribe to, we may ask for\nhealth symptoms, such as having a cough or a temperature\nAge and Gender\nOther self-reported data.\nAll the data is collected anonymously. We do not collect personal identifiable information.\nThe Information that you provide and we collect will be held in accordance with the Data Protection Act 2018 and the EU General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR). Your personal data will be collected and processed for the purpose of modelling.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_4">How We Use Your Information</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_5">Apart from the services offered to you to inform on your personal mobility, we will collate the data to form part of one or more scientific publications and studies which will inform research and policies related to health and wellbeing, computer science, city management, traffic management, defence and other related fields. Individuals personal data will not be identified or released in any report, publication or project output of any kind.\nThe data collected will be retained for the project purposes of scientific analysis. This data may be used in part to undertake scientific analysis which can result in informing public policy, practices, new technology and methodologies as well as supporting the development of new products and services.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_6">How Information Is Shared</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_7">The data will be accessed and analysed by researchers at The University of Sheffield and or other research institutions with a strict ethical code working with The University of Sheffield on specific programmes. We may use some companies or organisations to support us in the management of the data infrastructure. These companies or organisations will access the data for the sole purpose of maintaining the infrastructure and will not be allowed to use the data for any other reasons.\nNo personal data will be released in any form outside the University of Sheffield. Any external researcher accessing the data will have to do so from inside our firewall/premises and will not be allowed to export any data.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_8">Data Retention</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_9">Data held on your phone is deleted when the app is uninstalled. Data held on our server are deleted on explicit request from the user, using the feedback menu of the app. If this is not requested, data will be kept for a maximum period of 20 years. This time period is required because we aim to model mobility phenomena over very long term and hence your data remain useful in the long term.</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_link_default" translatable="false">@string/privacy_policy_link_en</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_link_en" translatable="false">http://api2.mobinmobility.org/moving-health-pis.html</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_link_default" translatable="false">@string/terms_and_conditions_link_en</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_link_en" translatable="false">https://aeqora.weebly.com/terms-and-conditions.html</string>
    <string name="troubleshooting_link_default" translatable="false">@string/troubleshooting_link_en</string>
    <string name="troubleshooting_link_en" translatable="false">http://setamobility.weebly.com/troubleshooting_en.html</string>
    <string name="find_nhs_number_link_default" translatable="false">https://www.nhs.uk/nhs-services/online-services/find-nhs-number/</string>
    <string name="policy_shown_key">policy shown</string>
    <string name="next">Continue</string>
    <string name="accept_privacy">Accept The Privacy Policy?</string>

    <string name="onboarding_description_first_install">In order to use the %1$s app, some permissions and the privacy policy need to be accepted. Please click on the continue button and follow the next steps to complete the configuration</string>
    <string name="onboarding_location_0"><![CDATA[In order to accurately record your activity the app needs to access the Physical Activity and Location data stored on your mobile device.\nPlease follow the instructions below when the permissions are shown.]]></string>
    <string name="onboarding_location_1"><![CDATA[1. Allow the app to access your physical activity?\n2. Click on Allow.]]></string>
    <string name="onboarding_location_2"><![CDATA[The app collects location data to enable accurate activity tracking even when the app is closed or not in use. For each of your activities a map is provided showing the route followed for a specific activity.\nPlease tick the box below to enable location detection and then select "While Using the App"]]></string>
    <string name="onboarding_location_4">Allow background location detection by ticking the box below and then selecting "Allow All the Time:"</string>
    <string name="physical_activity">Physical Activity *</string>
    <string name="physical_activity_permission">I agree to give access to my physical activity data. This does not include any GPS data.</string>
    <string name="accept_tcs">Accept Terms and Conditions?</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="open_battery_permissions">"Open App Info"</string>
    <string name="battery_permissions">"Battery Settings"</string>
    <string name="battery_settings_description"><![CDATA[The app has to run continuously in order to collect accurate data.\n\nClick on Check Settings and follow the instructions below:\n\n1. Open the Settings app on your device and select Battery (or Battery Management or Battery usage)\n2. Select No restrictions (typically it is top item)]]></string>
    <string name="battery_drainage_description"><![CDATA[In the future, your device may display a message informing you that the app uses power in the background and may drain the battery. Ignore that warning. The app has to run continuously in order to collect more accurate data]]></string>
    <string name="A_R_description">In order to accurately record your activity the app needs to access the data from the Physical Activity sensor.</string>

    <string name="battery_permissions_removal">"Open App Settings"</string>
    <string name="battery_permissions_removal_description"><![CDATA[If you do not open the app for a few days, Android is likely to stop the app\nClick on Check Settings and untick the option Remove Permissions if app is unused]]></string>
    <string name="battery_permissions_removal_open">"Open App Settings"</string>
    <string name="permission_removal_unticked_key">battery_removal_unticked</string>
    <string name="onboarding_finalised">onboarding_finalised</string>
    <string name="battery_optimised">battery_optimised</string>
    <string name="t_and_c_key">term_and_conditions</string>
    <string name="start_tracker">Start Tracker</string>
    <string name="stop_tracker">Stop Tracker</string>
    <string name="email_body">Here are the files from the active sensors</string>
    <string name="email_subject">"Sensor results "</string>
</resources>